Manciulea Victor

Brasov, Strada Zizinului 91,scara A,apartament 14

0733401436

vmanciulea@gmail.com

Additional Skills

I played professional basketball in my hometown.I was registered at the team for 7 years and I could say that there I learned about the importance of teamwork.

- pragmatic
- · fast learner
- patient
- easy-going

Professional Summary

I started working in this industry as a lobby boy at a 5* hotel in my hometown called Aro Palace. Front office wasn't for me, however I acquired a lot of hospitality skills by working as a lobby boy, so I decided to try to be a waiter. My first job was at a poker saloon in Brasov, where I was a waiter/bartender, I took orders from the customers and I had to prepare the bevereges and serve the dishes. After that at a pub/cafe in the historic center of Brasov called Museum, which I didn't particularly like because it wasn't as frequented as I expected so I decided to try to work at a ski resort called Sinaia, as a waiter helper, where I learned a lot about customer service from experienced waiters with which I had the pleasure to work.I hadn't worked under a legal contract at this restaurant. The next job I had also was in the historic center of Brasov, called Aftar Stube, where I was a waiter. From my time there, where I had the pleasure to work with some of the best bartenders in Brasov and in my personal opinion the best in my country, despite the fact that I was a waiter. I learned a lot about bartending. With the information and skill I optained by watching and practicing along side them, I took a job as a bartender at the most frequented bistro lounge in Brasov called Bistro AHA. After the summer season finale and a long consideration, I decided that it is time to perfect my skills abroad.

Work Experience

vvoik Experience	
Hotel Aro Palace,Brasov lobby boy	06/2014-05/2016
Spoker,Brasov bartender/waiter at a poker saloon	06/2016-04/2017
Museum Pub,Brasov bartender	05/2017-02/2018
Aftar Stube,Brasov waiter	09/2018-05/2019
Bistro AHA,Brasov bartender	06/2019-09/2019

Education

09/2010-05/2014

Natural Science Highschoool "Emil Racovita", Brasov

- mathematics
- informatics

Languages